sandobaggu ni
On the sandbag
ukande kieru nikui anchikushou no kao megake
I can see the face of the man I hate.
tatake! tatake! tatake!
Punch! Punch! Punch!
oira nya kemono no chi ga sawagu
The blood of the beast in me boils
dakedo...
But...
ashita wa kitto nani ka aru
Something will happen tomorrow
ashita wa docchi da
Which way is tomorrow?
Those are the Eyes of a Wild Animal!
Episode 1
It's cold!
It's cold, isn't it?
I'm freezing!
Maybe we should start a fire.
Yeah, let's do that. Geez, it's cold.
What are you doing about work today?
Here I go!
Hey, wait up!
I said wait!
Give it back!
Hey! Someone, stop them!
Wait!
Dammit!
Someone bring me a drink!
Damn it all...
Give me a drink...
What do you think this is?
Hey, wait!
I said wait!
That's an order!
You guys can't catch me!
Who's that?
Who does he think he is?
He's just another bum.
Run!
Wait for me!
Is that the drifter you were talking about?
Yeah.
All right, everyone follow me.
Right!
Why, you...
Hey, you little brats!
What do you want?
If you want something, quit sneaking
around and show yourselves!
If I'm in the mood, I'll play with you.
So what do you say, big guy?
Yikes!
T-Tarou-chan, that guy's pretty good.
If you don't want anything, I'm leaving.
You bum!
We don't allow tabs!
If you want to drink, bring money!
C'mon mister, don't say that. Just one drink...
Quit hounding me! Just get lost!
Alright...
Hey, Mister...
What's your problem?
Hold it.
Hey, youngster.
I haven't seen you around here before.
You a drifter?
Well, whatever.
Sorry, but could you lend me some money?
One or two hundred yen would be fine.
It'd really help me out, young'un.
Come on!
Don't touch me!
What'd you say, you bastard!
Don't screw around with me!
Hey! Everyone, look!
That guy started a fight with Kenkichi.
That guy's starting to get interesting.
Old man, you think you can fight when you're that drunk?
Did you see that?
He beat Kenkichi with one blow!
That's why I told you to give up, old man.
If you're gonna beg, do it when you're sober.
Geez, old man...
You still won't give up.
Then I'll just have to hit you again!
That's good.
You got a pretty good punch, eh?
What'd ya say we team up?
You wanna come do boxing with me?
Boxing?
That's right, boxing.
You could do it.
If I coached you, you could definitely do it.
Give it a try!
Forget it.
What? You don't wanna team up with me and try boxing?
Kenkichi's at it again!
Eh, young man?
You don't shut up, do you?
Stay away from me, old man.
You reek of booze.
No! Let me go!
No! No!
I said no!
I said let me go! Let me go!
You're so noisy. Be quiet already.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Let me go! Let me go!
Just shut up already, you little brat!
Oh no, Sachi got caught!
This is trouble!
The Onihime Group!
Hey, what should we do?
What should we do, you say?
What can we do?
There's nothing we can do...
Hey, move it, little man. You're in the way.
What's that? "Move it," you say?
You aren't back in Ginza, you know!
Hold it!
If you guys walk side-by-side like that
on this narrow road, no one can get by.
If you guys really want to get by,
go ahead and walk on the roof,
or in the gutter, or wherever you like, got it!?
It looks like you guys just don't get it.
Hey, young man, you're really looking to get hurt, aren't you?
Who's going to get hurt?
What?
Mister, you'd better stop. Stop!
These guys do nothing but bad things
all day for the Onihime Group!
Why you little...
Talking shit when you're just a little thief yourself!
What do you want!?
Wh-What?
Stop it!
I'm not a thief! I just took a little bit of oden!
Ouch!
Liar!
You stole all the money from the cart and ran away!
That's a lie!
It was just oden!
Why you little...
Ouch!
It hurts!
Sachi!
Well, you see how it is.
Now we need to take her to her dad and have a little talk.
Get it now, boy?
We have to pass through this road.
Then go through the ditch.
What?
Wait!
You little...
Oh, this is the punch!
This killer, powerful punch!
These eyes of mine...
These eyes of mine have no doubt!
I've found it!
I've finally found it!
That was cool!
Mister!
Um... here!
Thank you very much.
Hey, mister, what's your name?
Me?
Well, it's not really worth mentioning, but...
Joe. Yabuki Joe.
Joe! Cool!
Yup, that's what it is.
Little Miss Oden Thief.
Th-Thie...
Oh, that's quite the face you're making!
Perhaps you need to go to the bathroom?
Well, whatever.
Next time, don't just steal a little bit of oden,
steal the entire stand!
People have to think big, you know!
Wait, you blockhead!
Ow! Wh-Who did that?
Wait!
Dammit!
Stop it!
What are you talking about, saying "thief" and "bathroom"?
Is that any way to talk to a lady?
Lady? Oh, is that so?
I'm very sorry.
I was out of line. Please forgive me.
That is... Well, if you apologize so much, I feel bad...
But you really should hurry to the bathroom.
Or are you still wearing diapers?
Diapers? Why... you...
Dammit!
See you later, Princess!
Dammit! Dammit!
Diapers...
Well, he went and made her cry.
There's no mistake.
It's him!
He's the one I've been searching for all this time!
Joe... Yabuki Joe!
Whoa, whoa... Just a moment, sir.
Sorry, but we ask our guests to pay first.
Hello, are you the owner?
Thanks for having me.
I'm just so exhausted right now...
That'll be 150 yen.
That's so cheap, but I don't have any
small change on me at the moment.
Hey, we have a guest leaving!
No, no, no, get out!
People with no money should be sleeping under bridges or in the park!
Come on, Miss...
You'd throw this poor young man out into the cold?
What "poor young man"? You're a strong young man!
If you want to sleep under a roof,
you have to work hard during the day!
I know,
so I'll clean your halls or do whatever you-
SHUT UP!
Cheapskate.
Hey, young man, you'll catch a cold sleeping in a place like this.
Won't you put yourself in the care of Tange Danpei?
You won't regret it.
I'll train you to box properly.
If I coach you, you'll become a first-rate boxer!
Then you won't have to sleep on the streets.
You'll have a fancy car and
live in a big house with a pool!
Even you would be happy with that, right, Joe?
Man, I'm surprised how crazy you are about boxing.
Even if the kid is that promising,
it wasn't worth giving up your coat.
For a boxer, the body is the most important thing.
If he sleeps out in this cold-
Well, well, it looks like you're catching a cold.
Here, have a drink of this and warm up.
Oh, that...
What's the matter?
I quit drinking.
What?
Is this about boxing again?
Why don't you give it up already, old man?
No...
He'll definitely become a boxer.
He's a bit stubborn, but there's no way my sincerity won't reach him.
Your sincerity, you say?
Stop being so naive...
Joe!
I looked all over for you, old man.
See, look, he came after all!
I came to give back your dirty coat, old man!
And the oden was a little cold, but thanks anyway.
Yes, yes. Wasn't it good?
And there's one more thing.
Go ahead! What is it?
If you come near me again, it won't be pretty!
I can't stand drunken bums.
I don't drink anymore!
Since I saw your punch this afternoon, I quit... completely.
Do you understand?
That's how strongly I feel about your punch.
I'm ready to put everything on the line for you.
So young'un, Yabuki Joe, let me train you!
Okay?
Tange Danpei, was it?
Now that I think about it, there used to be a boxer
by that name, though he wasn't very strong.
That was a long time ago...
So you think you can revive the old dream with that dirty face?
What?
Hold it, old man.
If you have time to fight me,
you should hurry up and get out of here.
Joe, run away!
You don't know what these guys can do!
If you want to run, then run. These guys are my guests.
So this is the guy that beat up three of our men.
As expected, you've got a lot of guts, boy.
I'd rather you compliment my skill, not my guts.
Joe, you idiot! Don't get them mad!
You guys, get lost already!
Get him!
Why, you...
Bring it on!
You bastard!
Amazing! He's amazing!
It's a dream! It's like a dream!
That's it, Joe!
That's it!
That's it! Right! Left!
Throw a right! Right! Yes! Like that!
Don't kick, you idiot!
This isn't kickboxing! Use your hands! Your hands!
That's it! That's good. Like that!
Good work! Keep going! One more!
You seem to be enjoying this, old man.
I have something to ask.
Won't you turn him over to
the Onihime Group? He'd be a great-
Shut up! Are you kidding?
Don't be stupid!
Can't you see the light in his eyes?
Those aren't the filthy eyes of a yakuza.
Those are the eyes of a wild beast looking towards tomorrow!
Everyone, that's enough!
Stop it.
What? You're done already?
That was hardly a warm-up.
I'm just saying playtime is over.
Everyone, draw your weapons.
Bastard.
Dammit.
Oh no!
Knives are no good! Please! Just don't use knives!
Please! I'm begging you!
Old man, you look pathetic.
Idiot! How long do you think you can be so cocky for?
There's a tide in the affairs of men. Can't you see it's waning!?
You could be killed!
It's not "could be"!
I have every intention of killing him.
That's just as it should be.
Idiot!
This is okay.
This is...
Try to kill him if you want,
but I won't let you lay a finger on him while I'm still alive!
If you're gonna kill him, you'll have to kill me first!
You bastard... Talking so big...
All right, everyone, beat this old man up and get him off!
Right!
Why you...
There, take that!
You bastard!
Move it!
Why, you!
Move already.
Hey, old man, let me go!
You just keep quiet!
You're gonna be a boxer, got it?
You're gonna team up with me and start boxing!
You will!
Shut up, you lunatic! Let me go!
I'll never let you go!
You're my tomorrow...
Tomorrow's Joe!
I'm not gonna let you go!
What's this "tomorrow" crap!?
Let me go!
You're talking crazy.
Let go of me!
Let me go, dammit!
Let me go!
I met him that day...
The man with the eyes of a wild beast, Yabuki Joe.
I saw his punch and decided to train him,
but he wouldn't go along with me.
Despite my protests, he started a fight with the Onihime Group.
NEXT EPISODE
Life in the Square Jungle
Now, which way is tomorrow for Tomorrow's Joe?
kinou hagureta ookami ga
The stray wolf of yesterday
kyou wa matto de chi wo nagashi
spills blood on the mat today.
ashita wo mezashite tachiagaru
Get up and aim for tomorrow!
tate!
Get up!
tate, tate!
Get up, get up!
tatsunda Joe!
Get up, Joe!
komori uta wa ringu nya naize!
There are no lullabies in the ring!
tattanakya kino ni gyaku modori
If you don't get up, you'll fall back to yesterday.