sandobaggu ni
On the sandbag
ukande kieru nikui anchikushou no kao megake
I can see the face of the man I hate.
tatake! tatake! tatake!
Punch! Punch! Punch!
oira nya kemono no chi ga sawagu
The blood of the beast in me boils
dakedo...
But...
ashita wa kitto nani ka aru
Something will happen tomorrow
ashita wa docchi da
Which way is tomorrow?
Life in the Square Jungle
Episode 2
Yabuki Joe, get out here.
We have some questions.
Yabuki, what's the matter!?
Don't call my name out so rudely.
I'm the victim here.
At least, call me Yabuki-san.
Cut the bullshit! A poor victim?
Even though they were yakuza,
you sent fifteen people to the hospital!
Fifteen? That's it?
Shut your big mouth!
Old man Danpei saved you
from being hacked to pieces like a fish!
Yeah right!
If he wasn't there, I could've showed 'em how strong I am!
If you're gonna kill him,
you'll have to kill me first!
Shut up, you lunatic! Let me go!
Let me go!
What a meddler...
Yabuki! Danpei's bedridden from those nasty injuries!
The only reason you're getting out of here is
because he volunteered to be your guardian.
Huh? I see. What a useless meddler!
Well then...
Don't make me laugh!
You surprised me!
Well, if it isn't Sachi! What're you doin' here?
Nothing much. Just passing by...
What?
You were worried about me, weren't you?
N-No way! Who'd care about you!?
You're trying to hide it, but I know you do.
W-What!? Why...
Why you stupid, silly, snotty, handsome idiot!
Well, that's true, but...
Oh, okay, my mistake then.
I liked you so much though.
Oh, you don't have to confess your love so boldly...
Damn, what a forward kid! It's embarrassing.
Enough playing around.
Take me to where your friends are.
Today, I've got some good news to tell you!
Listen carefully!
In short, I've decided to make you guys my followers!
Geez! That's too sudden! It's so one-sided!
How can he decide that so suddenly?
Like he can decide that!
What!?
I guess it's okay...
Wait!
Right, then it's decided.
Now, let's have a round of applause!
Good, good! That's enough!
This is great, don't you think so?
He thinks he's pretty big, doesn't he?
Yeah, yeah.
Now then...
Well, it's time for our first job!
Who is it!?
W-Well, there's a guest for the boss.
Hey, Hirata. What's going on?
I don't have any appointments today.
I'll see.
Let him in.
P-Please.
Ouch!
Y-You!
Don't worry, I didn't come here to fight.
Boss, he's the punk from the other night, that Joe guy!
Get 'im, guys!
Hold it!
Put away the blades! He said he wasn't here to fight.
So you're Oniyama?
You're a fast learner.
State your business.
My boss, Tange Danpei, was mercilessly beaten by your men,
so I'm collecting the hospital expenses for—
What the hell!?
Wait, Hirata.
How much?
A million yen
is what I'd ask for, but since this is our first time,
I'll give you a big discount and drop it to 300,000.
A little expensive.
He got beaten up badly and is crippled for life. It's cheap.
I'll give you thirty thousand.
Thirty thousand?
I have no problem with thirty thousand,
but only on one condition.
One condition?
Join us and start working for me from today on.
The thirty thousand is your hiring fee.
Cut the crap! You gonna pay the compensation or not!?
Boys, shut his mouth. Permanently!
Ouch!
All of you, take a good look out the window.
You! What're those kids doing!?
If I drop this handkerchief,
when it flutters down, the fire engines will go "WOO WOO," police cars will go "NAAA," and they'll all bust in here!
This building will be like a madhouse!
Boss, what should we do?
Give him the money.
Yes sir.
Here!
Thanks a lot.
See ya!
Hey, officer, it's an emergency!
That punk! He played me like a fool.
Compensation?
I can't believe that the Onihime Group paid that.
Well, you did save my life, so I went and
did some tough negotiating with them.
Here!
I see. You're a kinder person than I thought.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
Have a look at this too.
What's this?
"Invoice For Services Rendered"?
"1. Negotiation fee for compensation: 10,000 yen.
2. Recovery fee for mental stress caused by endangerment: 5,000 yen.
3. Fee for kids: 2,000 yen.
4. Miscellaneous expenditures: 3,000 yen.
For a total of 20,000 yen for services rendered."
And there you have it, thanks a lot.
W-What "negotiation"!?
You used me for money! You scumbag!
Yup! That's what they call me.
So, you'd better stop chasing me around
or you'll be sorry in the end.
Get it, old man?
You came here to threaten me?
Sorry, but I'm not leaving you alone.
Since I've become the guardian of Yabuki Joe,
it's my duty to keep an eye on you at all times!
And I'll definitely turn you into a boxer!
You won't give up, no matter what?
I'll never give up! Never!
Then do as you wish.
YOU...!
There you go!
There!
C'mon, keep it up!
Here! Another box!
There!
Here you go!
All right!
Got it!
There!
That bastard!
He's winning all of our profits! We gotta do something!
But we can't just kick out a customer, it'll look bad!
Excuse us, let the Tange family through!
Let us through!
The Tange family!?
Damn that Joe!
I know what you're trying to do.
You're gonna use him as a thug for a new gang, huh?
That's why you became his guardian, right?
The fact that you aren't qualified to be his guardian is very clear now!
THAT'S NOT TRUE!
Let me take care of him!
No matter what happens, I'll...
Come on, guys! We've got everything
from daily necessities to luxury items.
Excuse me.
These cookies are cheap, only 30 yen?
If you bought them in a supermarket,
it'd cost you more than 100 yen!
You buying 'em, kiddo?
Of course, it's a great deal!
Here!
Thanks, kiddo.
Hooray! I've never seen cookies this cheap before!
I'm so lucky today!
That was surprising!
While so many adults hesitate to buy
that young boy immediately realized a great deal.
The future of Japan looks bright!
So, how was that?
I-Idiot! You came back too early!
What a bad scam!
Anyway, they're pretty cheap, so I'll take one.
Give me a dozen of those chocolates.
Give me some cigarettes.
A box of dry fish, please.
There they are!
Let's go have a look!
Hey, ladies, don't leave yet, you haven't finished shopping!
It's Joe! That bastard, Joe!
What!?
Come on, special offers here! Really cheap!
Let us through! Go away! What the hell are you doing here!?
You sure are determined to be annoying
and interfere with our business, eh?
B-Boss!
I was waiting for you guys.
Bastards! Come on!
Who the hell are you?
Take this!
Another one!
Joe, stop it!
Come on!
You bastard...
I'll have mercy on you for today.
Let's go!
They're running away!
Hold on!
You getting in our way again, old man? Kill 'im!
Joe, get outta here! Run for it!
Joe, run for it! You can't let them injure your body!
Run away Joe, you will box for me...
Joe, get outta here!
Joe...
Joe!
Ouch!
That's why I told you, old man,
to quit following me around.
Why don't you just give up?
I don't have the slightest interest in boxing.
Well, I'd think about it if you were offering money.
Joe, will you listen to my old story?
Old story?
Is the ex-boxer going to tell me about his glorious past?
I don't wanna hear the same old story.
You're right, it's the same old story.
You're right, but for me...
You bastard! What're ya waitin' for!?
Come on, hit, hit, you idiot! Stupid!
For me, the ring was my whole life.
Or should I say, without the ring, I was nothing.
Even after I lost my eye,
which is a fatal injury for a boxer, and retired
What are you doing!?
I still hung onto the ring as a coach.
You coward! Gutless idiot!
You! Get in here!
Gimme a break already, Coach!
What?
I said, gimme a break!
Stop kicking and yelling at me! I'm not your cat or dog!
Why you little...!
My girlfriend watches the fights on TV.
I didn't look good at all! Damn!
Don't screw around with me!
You bastard!
What?
You knew you were down on points in the final round,
why didn't you go all out!?
Are you kidding?
If I charged in and got hurt, I'd look even worse!
What!?
How many times do I have to tell you!?
If you aren't hungry to win, you won't succeed in the ring!
If you don't win, you won't get food for tomorrow!
The strong prey upon the weak!
That's the law of the square jungle!
Win or lose!
Then what did the ex-boxer who followed
that law, Tange Danpei, get in the end
other than a blind eye and a scarred face?
Shut up, you damn fool!
I'm through with you.
I've been offered a deal from a new and bigger boxing gym!
Wait!
Please wait!
It was my last day with the ring.
Since I lost my eye on the verge of winning the title match,
I vowed to create a champion boxer of my very own, at the very least,
but I fell into debt.
And my last boxer, who I trained so rigorously, left me.
I'm a loser.
A loser who just threw his whole life into boxing.
Who didn't even get married and have any children.
And this loser drifted around,
finding a suitable home in this dump.
I drank.
Booze was my only relief.
But, ironically,
the more I drank, the more I remembered boxing.
Bring me some booze!
I became a pathetic excuse for a man.
That's when I saw you and,
in your eyes, those eyes of a wild beast.
I saw the true light I'd been searching a long time for.
Joe, I'm now... betting everything on you.
Joe?
They're here.
Please, listen to me just a little longer!
I've been waiting!
Get him!
Joe, stop it!
Don't interrupt me this time, old man.
Well, you can't do anything in your condition anyway.
Wait!
Wait, Joe!
Don't be stupid!
JOOOOOE!
Can't keep up, eh?
Looks like you brought everyone, didn't you?
We're gonna end this once and for all.
Don't worry, same here.
It's a damn shame; you got guts and fight well.
Well, enjoy your previous victories while you can
because we're gonna teach you just
how terrifying the Onihime Group can be!
You bastard!
That hurt!
Bastard!
You bastard!
Joe, are you all right? Joe!
Joe, hang in there!
Joe!
Hang in there!
Hey! Old man Kenkichi!
What're you doing looking like that?
Where're you going?
Joe, don't be stupid!
Your body isn't yours alone!
You... You are my precious tomorrow!
Hurry, hurry! What's keeping you?
What'll we do if Joe's killed!?
No way Joe'll be killed that easily!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Listen, Joe...
You're everything to me now.
You can't... You can't die on me now!
JOE!
Where are you!?
Joe's... Joe's not here!
Where's Joe!?
Joe!
That goddamned Joe...
He completely destroyed the Onihime Group...
Hey, old man.
What pathetic bastards.
All these men,
and they couldn't even lay a finger
on me before dropping dead.
Guess I was too strong for them.
They couldn't even lay a single finger on you at all?
Then what're all those marks on
your face and the blood on your hands?
Y-You...
You made me worry so much!
Are you satisfied now?
I'm asking you if you're satisfied now!
YOU...
stupid idiot...
Thank goodness you're safe!
I'm so relieved!
How does three meals, a nap, and 500 yen
for pocket money per day sound?
What do you mean by that?
Listen up.
Those are my conditions for boxing.
What? What did you say?
You're...
Is 500 yen a day too cheap?
No, not at all! But, more importantly,
a-are you really going to box?
Yeah, I meant what I said.
Joe...
I see! You finally understand my feelings!
All right, let's do it!
You'll see.
I'll make you the number one boxer in Japan; no, the world!
I don't mind your excitement,
but don't forget my conditions, old man.
Joe started to practice boxing under my tutelage.
Of course, under the agreement of three meals, a nap,
and 500 yen for pocket money per day.
I quit drinking completely,
and started working at construction sites during the
day and road construction at night with all of my might
for Joe's tomorrow,
and to build a great boxing gym for us!
But Joe takes advantage of a beautiful young girl,
Shiraki Yohko, who is the granddaughter
of the Shiraki Corporation's chairman.
I'm starting to wonder if it was
a mistake to bet everything on him.
Now,
which way is tomorrow for Tomorrow's Joe!?
NEXT EPISODE
Fangs of the Beast Exposed!
kinou hagureta ookami ga
The stray wolf of yesterday
kyou wa matto de chi wo nagashi
spills blood on the mat today.
ashita wo mezashite tachiagaru
Get up and aim for tomorrow!
tate!
Get up!
tate, tate!
Get up, get up!
tatsunda Joe!
Get up, Joe!
komori uta wa ringu nya naize!
There are no lullabies in the ring!
tattanakya kino ni gyaku modori
If you don't get up, you'll fall back to yesterday.