sandobaggu ni
On the sandbag
ukande kieru nikui anchikushou no kao megake
I can see the face of the man I hate.
tatake! tatake! tatake!
Punch! Punch! Punch!
oira nya kemono no chi ga sawagu
The blood of the beast in me boils
dakedo...
But...
ashita wa kitto nani ka aru
Something will happen tomorrow
ashita wa docchi da
Which way is tomorrow?
Fangs of the Beast Exposed!
Episode 3
One, two, one, two, three!
Harder!
Stronger!
One, two, one, two!
Black Cat's Tango, Tango, Tango...
Hey, they keep on doing it!
One, two, one, two, three!
Joe! You're so great! Cool!
Hey, kids! You came!
Hey, quit looking around and train seriously!
Seriously!
Okay, okay.
One, two!
Stronger!
No, that's no good at all!
Don't just hit with your arms!
Put your hips into it, your hips!
Even he gets spanked!
How should I put my hips into it? Like this?
Listen,
to put your hips into it...
Hey, hold that bag firmly!
Sure thing.
Look at me. First, I lower my hips,
and then I spring up with my knees!
How 'bout that?
Swinging your hips concentrates all the power of your body into your arm.
It's the timing.
Go on, try it.
I'm fine.
That was quite the punch.
Let's see...
Now I'll throw mine.
First, lower my waist, and then spring up with my knees.
What is that?! Come on, that looks horrible!
Joe looks cooler than you!
Why you...!
Shut up, brats! Go away!
Was my punch a little too strong?
Well, this is what happens if I get a little serious.
Mister, that sandbag is broken,
so today's practice is over, right?
Not a chance. Now we practice mitt punching.
C'mon. If you miss, I won't let you off easy!
Okay, okay.
Right, that's the idea!
C'mon, gimme everythin' ya got!
Wha...?
Damn, I did it again.
It's too early to go to sleep, old man!
Wake up, old man! It's the 8 o'clock siren.
Huh? Already 8?
Right, time to go to work.
If you show up late, they'll lower your pay. Hurry up. Come on!
Okay, okay.
Old man Kenkichi is working now?
What made him change his mind?
He used to sell his blood and get drunk every day.
I guess old man Kenkichi wanted to do boxing seriously, so he quit drinking.
I'm going now.
Wait a sec, old man.
Before you go, haven't you forgotten something?
Huh?
You know, "three meals, a nap, and..."
I know: "500 yen per day pocket money."
The agreement between me and you for boxing, right?
Exactly. Thank you.
So greedy...
See ya later!
Listen, don't forget your homework!
Run between here and the gas tank,
jump rope 3000 times, and-
I know, I know. Now go!
Training, training...
Good luck at work, old man!
Thank you so much, Grandpop!
Make use of that ox-like build of yours!
Now the fussy geezer is gone.
Now then, time to put away the earnings for today.
Hey, Joe, what are you doing?
Saving.
Saving? To buy a new sandbag or something?
No, it's for my big plan.
What's the plan?
A very good thing.
I can't really tell you though.
Joe, can I ask you a few questions?
What is this, an interview?
Why do you always speak so snobbily?!
They're just normal questions!
You hated boxing so much,
tell me why you suddenly
decided to start boxing?
I didn't hate it, it was just
that I wasn't interested in it.
I'm not doing this seriously anyway.
If I take his offer,
he'll be happy and give me three meals, a nap,
and 500 yen pocket money per day.
Do you think there's any better jobs here?
Hey, Joe's way more evil than I thought.
Yeah, way worse than us.
Joe, I finally found you.
You were born to be a boxer.
Speed, punch, intuition...
Just like a wild beast!
But it's not enough.
You need training!
Strict practice will make you a bona fide boxer.
You will understand true boxing
when you finish your difficult training.
Do your best, Joe!
I'll work hard and build a great gym for you.
According to the training schedule I made,
maybe you're running to the gas tank right now.
After that, you'll jump rope 3000 times, then do sit-ups.
Keep it up, Joe!
Don't forget your weaving practice.
That's it, like that! Joe, do your best!
You will get over the suffering of training together with me
and jump into the world of boxing!
Joe... you are my tomorrow!
Go! Joe! Great!
Hey, look at this! Just like that!
And a turn and... here!
Wow! Cool! More!
That's it for today.
This little girl will come around now, so give her a little change, okay?
Okay, thank you very much.
Thanks as always!
Hey, you have a 100 yen coin there. Give it to her!
Thank you very much! We'll be here
again tomorrow, so come back soon!
Wow, he's become a different person!
I've heard that he's devoted the rest of his life
to a young man named Joe or something.
"Joe," you say?
He's supposed to become a world champion.
What a dreamer!
Joe, it's all about the training, got it?!
Today's pay?
I'm going now.
Don't forget the homework.
See ya later.
It's strangely quiet today.
Hey, what's up, you two?
You look rich today.
Where did you steal that balloon from?
How rude! Accusing me of stealing!
These are presents from Shiraki Yohko-san.
Shiraki Yohko? Who's that?
She comes here every month and gives us lots of presents.
They say she's a charitable person.
A charitable person?
I bet she's a single old woman and
is trying to impress men to get married!
But, she's very kind.
Heh, you're a kid after all.
People are only nice to you when they're gonna use you.
Where is this woman who deceives children?
Over there.
Whaddya think? Ain't she pretty?
See? Pretty, ain't she?
She's no big deal.
That's it. Everyone put out your hands.
Great, tomorrow's paper will feature
Shiraki Yohko, the charitable flower of the slums!
"The Charitable Flower of the Slums"?
Don't make me laugh!
What did you say?
Now listen, if you ever
take charity from that bitch,
I won't take care of you anymore!
T-Take it easy, boss. She just likes
to give things away. There's no harm.
That's right! We're being polite
in accepting her offer!
"Being polite"? I see...
Ya got me.
You're right. She's tossing them out
because she has plenty.
That's right, she's nice.
Shiraki Yohko-san,
who gives love to the poor, huh?
Okay, let's give it a go!
I'm all covered in dirt and sweat.
But Joe, when I think about your hard training,
I'm pleased to do this backbreaking labor!
Danpei-san, is it about Joe again?
Don't work too hard, or you'll hurt yourself.
I'm fine, this body has been through
tough training for boxing; I won't die so easily.
Not before tomorrow comes for me and Joe!
Joe ran off, didn't he?
Damn it, when you get back, I'll make you jump rope 5000 times, get it?!
Ouch!
Wh-What are these?!
All this money?
That bastard didn't...
Joe!
Hello?
I'm with the police.
W-Wait a minute, I'm sorry!
He didn't do anything!
It's just a mistake...
Just a mistake, really...
What are you talking about?
Did that kid do something bad?
N-No, no, not at all!
That's right.
I'm here to warn you about that kid before he does something horrible.
I mean, I don't know how much you know about Yabuki Joe,
but recently he's been taking a bunch of kids from the slums and leading them around town.
He cheats everyone! Fish shops, balloon shops, you name it. There are victims everywhere!
Anyway, if these things continue, as the police, we can't ignore it.
When he gets back, make sure you let him know about this, okay?
Y-Yes sir!
Farewell!
Young people these days, what are they thinking?
Joe, you bastard!
No, he's not that type of a guy!
He must have kept the money
I gave him without using it at all.
That's it! He must have been saving money to build a boxing gym for us!
There's no way he would betray me.
That's right, that can't happen!
Wow, what a huge, fancy house!
Yeah, incredible!
Joe, can we go home? I don't like
being in such a fancy place!
I am Shiraki Yohko, how may I help you?
The truth is,
I... No, we came here to see you today because
I heard that you were a friend of the poor like us.
These kids used to be in an orphanage.
It was run by a philanthropist,
but when the owner died, they were all
separated and sent to foster homes.
But nobody understood them and how lonely they were,
so they ran away and came to me.
I really want to take care of them,
but my ability is limited financially.
Money?
Yes.
I understand.
I shall take care of it somehow.
Hello, is this the Maicho Times?
This is Shiraki Yohko. Please put me through to the news department.
Yes, that's right. Yes.
Thanks for the food!
Yummy!
And so their orphanage was closed,
and they were adopted by different families.
I see, adopted...
They were adopted, but nobody truly understood their suffering.
They were abused and kicked out, so they ended up coming back to me, their big brother.
Oh, so that's what happened.
I see, they came back to you.
So you have been taking care of them ever since?
Hey, who is Joe talking about today?
About us!
Then, the poor orphans, who were driven out of their homes, are us?
Shut up!
What did you say?
Nothing at all.
I didn't want to talk about this,
but the orphanage director was actually my late mother.
So, I really want to-
Your mother?
What a great person, honestly...
That's it!
"Yabuki, the young man who follows in the footsteps of his philanthropist mother
and takes care of orphans."
This could be good!
Yes, it could,
and the person who provides the support is the warm and caring Shiraki Yohko-san!
Hey, guys, come over here.
Taking pictures of us?
Joe, I'm too shy.
No thanks.
I said, come here!
Okay...
Yes, sir...
All right.
Sorry, these kids are just so shy.
All right, everyone smile!
Okay, here we go!
That's bright, isn't it?
Lunch time! Everybody stop!
Tange, it's lunch time.
Okay, I'll just eat here.
Huh? There?
He's just having a single bun again!
Yeah, and he works on subway construction all night. I'm surprised his body can keep up.
There you are.
Take this.
Sorry about this.
Don't be shy. My wife gets mad if I don't finish it.
Is that right? Thanks for everything!
Danpei-san,
did you know that this floor is going to be a sky high restaurant?
The only time we'll be here is before it's done.
When this building is completed,
I will invite you here!
Huh? You will?
Joe's punch will bring me
enough money to eat at restaurants.
My Joe will do it!
Again with that Joe story?
Thanks.
Not at all.
What's this?
What's this? What's this?
"Heartwarming story of the street"?
Helping the orphans?
The orphaned children
came back to Yabuki Joe and...
That bastard!
I read about that yesterday.
It's nice that there are
decent young people out there.
Today's paper said that they've collected over one million yen
from people all over the country.
One million yen?
What's the matter, Danpei-san?
Th-That bastard... H-How could he?!
Good. That's it. Serves you right, baby!
Shiraki Yohko, you're so stupid!
Just as I suspected, everyone soon learned the truth about Joe.
After deceiving the millionaire, Shiraki Yohko,
and stealing an enormous amount of money,
Joe has now locked himself and the kids in a ruined building outside of town.
For straightening out Joe's crooked mind,
for our tomorrow,
and for the day he stands in the ring,
I hit Joe with my own hands!
Now,
NEXT EPISODE
Shed Tears for the Burning Fist!
which way is tomorrow for battle-scarred Joe?
kinou hagureta ookami ga
The stray wolf of yesterday
kyou wa matto de chi wo nagashi
spills blood on the mat today.
ashita wo mezashite tachiagaru
Get up and aim for tomorrow!
tate!
Get up!
tate, tate!
Get up, get up!
tatsunda Joe!
Get up, Joe!
komori uta wa ringu nya naize!
There are no lullabies in the ring!
tattanakya kino ni gyaku modori
If you don't get up, you'll fall back to yesterday.