sandobaggu ni
On the sandbag
ukande kieru nikui anchikushou no kao megake
I can see the face of the man I hate.
tatake! tatake! tatake!
Punch! Punch! Punch!
oira nya kemono no chi ga sawagu
The blood of the beast in me boils
dakedo...
But...
ashita wa kitto nani ka aru
Something will happen tomorrow
ashita wa docchi da
Which way is tomorrow?
episode title here
Fangs of the Beast Exposed!
Episode 4
Isn't it touching? I hear they gathered more than a million yen from around Japan.
That's right. The granddaughter of the Shiraki Corporation donated 200,000 yen.
She's so generous!
Danpei-san, you're a lucky man to be living with such a great young man.
Be good to him; he'll take good care of you.
Joe!
Joe, that bastard!
Committing fraud!
Dammit! That idiot!
I'm working my ass off here, dammit!
How could you do this?!
You're not gonna get away with this!
So you're saying that this entire article is a lie?
Yes, we printed the article right away because the information was from you, but then...
That Yabuki guy is quite the delinquent.
The story about being the son of a dead orphanage director was a complete lie,
and those kids weren't orphans at all.
He gathered some kids from the neighborhood and made up the story.
The truth is, our boss is very angry about that false article.
If we print articles with lies like these,
our company's reputation could be affected.
I'll take full responsibility for this.
What? We didn't mean it that way...
Please leave Yabuki Joe to me.
I'll catch him and have him write an apology.
What's the matter with you?!
It doesn't matter if you have parents
or if you're an orphan; you're all still poor.
Now all of Japan feels pity and sends money.
Just appreciate it. Appreciate it.
But, Boss, I really think we've gone too far.
No way! This is just the beginning!
My goal is one hundred million yen!
O-One hundred million yen?!
Right, I plan on getting a hundred million yen.
He said a hundred million yen!
H-How much is a hundred million yen?
H-Hey, Boss! What're you
going to do with all that money?
You guys are so nosy.
I was about to tell you.
Come on!
What a dump...
Just wait, I'll build a huge building soon.
This place is just temporary! Don't be shy!
One, two.
He's so full of himself! I guess he suffers from delusions of grandeur.
Yeah.
Shut your mouth and follow me, got it?!
One, two, one!
What's with Sachi? All she does lately is suck up to Joe! Geez!
What?! You got a problem with that?
Uh-oh! She's holding up her shoe!
N-No problems here!
Okay, we're coming, we're coming.
So, what do you think? Not bad, eh?
This is my office. Come in!
Now then!
To begin, I'll show you something good.
Don't be too shocked.
Wow! Yikes! Whoa! That's amazing!
These are all 1,000 yen notes!
There, you see?
When I put my mind to it, this is what I get!
But,
if you get overwhelmed by this,
you won't make it big!
Now I'm going to tell you
the most important thing.
Listen carefully.
Why do I need a hundred million yen?
Troops, look out the window.
You can see Yabuki Joe's dream plan from here.
I can see our slums!
Ew, it's filthy!
It's kind of embarrassing.
This is all because of the
crappy government, isn't it?
There's my house!
It's tiny!
Geez, when I look at it from up here, it really is a dump.
I'm going to get rid of that entire area first.
Huh? Are you going to get rid of my house?
Wh-Why're you gonna do that?
Right there, in the middle of the slums, I'm gonna make a big amusement park.
Next to it, there'll be a free hospital.
Free?
All those bars will become a nursing home
and a kindergarten right next to it.
We'll have that junk store moved
and build a modern five-story apartment complex!
And then we'll build a factory by the river.
That will be the final touch.
With the factory, we can give the unemployed people jobs and the pleasure of working.
And this way, we can banish poverty completely.
Now, this is the blueprint!
It's a real paper plan!
Be quiet, Kinoko!
I call this dream plan, "Joe's Paradise."
So, that's it. What do you think?
Cool!
I'm asking if you're in or out!
Huh?!
So, what's your answer?
W-Well, the plan is so big,
we just don't know what to say...
It's great!
I just knew from the start you were going
to be somebody. I wholeheartedly approve!
Good! You're all in! Now let's start working!
Now, come with me.
Wh-Where are we going?
Isn't it obvious?
You're working for me now.
I can't have you looking so dirty and ragged!
I'm going to have some
nice suits made for all of you.
After that you'll start work. Let's go!
Hey! Suits! Blue suits!
This is getting interesting!
Dammit, that Joe!
Joe, get out here! Joe?!
That Joe...
That bastard... He hasn't been training at all!
What did I make this thing for?
He doesn't care about me at all, dammit.
That bastard...
Idiot!
How dare you take me for a fool!
Just wait till I find you! You'll be sorry!
You better be ready, I'm gonna kill you!
Joe, please...
don't make trouble for me.
I'm making money for us, aren't I?
All you had to do was train.
That was all, dammit.
Now, if you don't straighten up,
you're gonna be in big trouble!
You massive idiot!
Joe, please...
Please don't cause any more problems, Joe!
Please...
Please, Joe...
Hey, hey!
So you're saying there's no way
you'll make suits for us?
Please, don't be so hasty.
We simply require a referral by another customer before we can...
Why you bastard!
You're looking down on us
because we look poor!
You old geezer!
We have money!
No, no, it's not about money!
You see, we have over 100 years
of proud service, and while I hate to boast,
we're considered the best tailor in Japan.
We take high profile orders
from governors and...
Dammit, you make me sick!
Let's go somewhere else,
somewhere less fancy...
Shut up!
We're gonna get our suits made here, the same place as the governors!
Well, well. What good timing!
Hey, old man,
a recommendation from the granddaughter of the Shiraki Corporation should be enough, right?
Uh, yes, well...
There you have it. Can you introduce us, Miss?
Ouch!
That hurt.
Apologize! You big liar!
Get on your hands and knees
and apologize properly!
If you apologize, I'll forget about what you did, this time.
Apologize!
Shut the hell up!
Me? Apologize?!
You're the idiot that fell for it!
Don't act so high and mighty!
What's with that look?
I shall repeat myself once more.
If you apologize,
I shall not take you to the police.
Now, apologize!
Police?!
Joe, say you're sorry!
You'll be thrown into the slammer, Boss! Apologize!
You've gotta be kidding!
Who'd apologize to her?!
Angel of the slums indeed!
I thought you were gonna beg me
to return the money, but
"apologize"?!
Dammit!
I don't like it!
Listen up, there's such a thing as honor!
Is that all you have to say?
Call the police or whatever!
Nobody's gonna catch me!
Got it?!
Joe!
Don't worry.
She won't call the police.
She'd be showing the world how stupid she is.
Isn't that right?
She'd make the Shiraki Corporation look bad.
There's no way you could do that, right?
Isn't that so, Missy? Eh?
You,
are a piece of trash!
What?!
God dammit!
Go to the police!
Tell them if they don't want to get hurt,
they'd better leave me alone!
Please take me to the police immediately!
Huh?
What didn't you understand?!
I said take me to the police station.
I'm going to see the chief.
What is it? Don't surprise me like that!
Tange-san?
I've been waiting for you.
I'm a police officer.
P-Police?
You're the legal guardian of Yabuki Joe, correct?
Yes, that's right.
He's at the station now.
Can you come with us?
What did he do?
Fraud. Alleged fraud.
Fraud?!
No wonder I couldn't find you.
You bastard, you've gone
and done it now, haven't you?
Here we are, Tange-san.
Wh-What is this? What's all this commotion about?
What happened here?
This is a mess!
It sure is!
Come on, clear the way!
What happened here?
Chief!
We have an emergency!
Yabuki Joe has... has escaped!
What?! Escaped?
Joe escaped?
When we were questioning him
in the interrogation room,
several kids ran into the station
and threw stones at us.
It was chaos!
Yabuki tried to escape in the confusion,
so we tried to restrain him,
but he fought us off and got away.
I'm so sorry!
How could this happen?!
All these officers and you
couldn't hold onto one boy?
B-But it's not so easy to hold onto someone with a punch like that.
And he moves so fast,
there was no way we could hold him!
Well then, Tange-san, what are your thoughts on this?
I'll tell you now,
this is enough to ensure that he'll be sent to a juvenile detention center
for at least six months!
Six months?
That's right, and possibly longer!
What?!
You found Yabuki?!
Huh?! He's barricaded himself in a ruin?!
Yabuki! Yabuki!
Listen carefully.
Please surrender immediately.
Leave the kids behind and come out peacefully!
That Joe, he went and got my kid involved.
It's like a hostage situation!
Hey, look, that Danpei guy came!
Danpei-san!
You're Joe's guardian, aren't you?
What about my kid?
You better take responsibility!
What're ya gonna do
if something happens to my kid?
My kid is still very young.
Do something!
That's a dirty trick,
using children to make money!
You taught him how to do that, didn't you?
Joe...
You...
Okay, we're going to storm the building now. Take your positions!
Get your weapons and seal all of the exits!
Don't let an ant escape from there!
Are you ready, men?
Get ready to flush out those windows to avoid the stones
and approach the building.
They are kids, but they are cornered and desperate, so stay alert!
All right! Get ready!
Hey, wait! Where are you going?!
I-It's dangerous, stop!
Tange-san! It's dangerous, come back!
Chief,
I will bring Yabuki Joe to you.
I can't allow this to get any worse than it is!
Idiot!
They're desperate!
It's too dangerous to go in!
Come back!
What?
Even so, they would never hurt me! Don't worry.
Well, maybe they will...
Joe!
Hey, why don't you answer, huh?
Watch out!
Come back here, Tange-san!
Hang on, hang on.
That's the old man.
What do you want?!
Oh, I see, so this is how you did it.
Don't get in over your head, old man!
Too bad!
I'm here to bring you in!
Prepare yourself!
What's that?
You forced me to learn boxing, but when
you can't control me, you side with the police?
How you grownups behave is dirty!
Get lost already, dog!
Idiot! Do you think I can't control you?
Don't overestimate yourself, punk!
I'm tellin' ya, old man...
Just try and take a step forward!
You'll regret it!
What do you mean, "regret it"?
Dammit!
You're out of line, old man!
Back off, old man.
You bastard!
This is totally unforgivable!
I feel sorry for you, but get ready!
What's with that stance?
What are you going to do?
This!
"Get ready" indeed!
Even all those policemen couldn't catch me!
I won't say anything bad, go to your kotatsu and drink some tea.
That suits you better.
What was that?
I see. It's just like the cops said.
You're good at fighting.
I'll admit that.
You move well.
You punch solidly.
The old man is coming up!
This could get dangerous.
Go watch from the side.
Okay!
But how far can you really go against me?
Before you talk like a big man,
make sure you don't fall down the stairs again.
Dammit... I'm just getting started!
Dammit all!
I admit, I can believe you used to be a pro boxer.
That was pretty good, old man,
but now it's my turn.
After all, I have to show you everything I've learned from training!
I see you can still talk like a big man.
Well, I'll make it so you can't talk then.
Come on!
Why you...
Man, this isn't funny!
Hey, everyone, don't just sit there! Let's help Joe!
Shut up, brats!
If you really want to help Joe, help me!
Got it?!
For this idiot,
it's best he's sent to the juvenile detention center before it's too late.
Get it?
Don't make me laugh!
Nobody's goin' to jail!
If I have to die...
Mister?
Prison...
Prison must be cold, right?
Don't worry about it.
Now move aside.
Mister, you...
You're worried about him too!
Joe!
My Joe!
Give him back! Give him back! Joe!
Give him back!
My... My Joe!
Give me back my Joe!
A thick wall has come between us and Joe.
We're not even allowed to visit him.
I decided to teach him boxing via mail training.
That's the first step for the sake of tomorrow.
Joe, bear through your loneliness and live for a bright tomorrow!
Now,
for Joe and I, separated by cold iron bars,
which way is tomorrow?!
NEXT EPISODE
Next Week: For the Sake of Tomorrow!
Part 1